Azlen Elza

Cellphone 778-683-6059

Location Vancouver, BC, V5Z-3Z8

Email contact@azlen.me
Website https://azlen.me

SUMMARY

I am a young programmer with 9+ years of personal experience in web development, currently working in the field of machine learning and AI. I am interested in the future of human-computer interaction and creating artificial intelligence algorithms that do not replace humans but become a tool for human-computer collaboration.

INTERESTS

Artificial Intelligence Robotics Virtual Reality Typography
Cognitive Science Linguistics Logic Game Design

EDUCATION

Emily Carr University of Art and Design

Sep. 2018 - 2022

Bachelor of New Media Arts

- Built musical instrument using facial recognition to play sound based on your facial expression using Python and Max MSP
- Introduced to new methods of creativity and thinking through design problems

WORK EXPERIENCE

Research Assistant Feb. 2018 - Present

Emily Carr University of Art and Design

- Training variety of neural networks (GAN, VAE, RNN, etc.) on images, audio, and text
- Plotting NOAA sea surface temperature data for Queens museum exhibition
- Smaller projects involving computer vision, virtual reality, laser cutting, and rPI

CURRENT PROJECTS

Neural Network 3D Object Construction

Tools: Python, Tensorflow, Unity

• Working on projecting Pix2Pix output using depth prediction onto 3D space from multiple viewpoints to construct voxel representations of objects

Mobile App for learning Chinese Characters

Dec. 2018 - Present

Dec. 2018 - Present

Tools: Javascript, Vue, Node, Phonegap, Figma

• Cross-platform app developed in Phonegap for learning to read and write chinese characters (hanzi), with each character building off of previously learned characters

AI Business Card Designer

Aug. 2018 - Present

Tools: Python, Tensorflow, Javascript

• Experiments in AI and generative design to teach computer aesthetic principles

PAST PROJECTS

Facial Recognition Musical Instrument

Nov. 2018

Plays sound based off facial landmark detection using Python and MaxMSP.

Pattern Generator Feb. 2018

Using series of mirroring and rotational transformations, creates large patterns from 2x2 pixel blocks.

Embol Dec. 2017

Video game about social anxiety built for 48 hour game programming competition.

Interactive Comic Editor

Sep. 2017

Tool for creating interactive and responsive SVG webcomics.

Perceptual Shift Ambigram Font (1,200+ glyphs)

Mar. 2016

Font which combines two words into a single word that can be read as either (e.g. True+False).

Video Game Sprite Generator

Dec. 2015

Tool to create template and color scheme from which to generate pixelart sprite variations.

Collaborative Text Adventure

Jan. 2014

Players can add new paths to collaboratively write a choose-your-own-path text adventure.

Ghoti (pronounced "fish")

Apr. 2013

Tool that messes up the spelling of a word without changing the (theoretical) phonetic pronunciation.